[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guess the missing number from the following sequence: 3,6,7,14,15 ___, 31,62, 63. 126, 127.", "correct_answer": "30", "incorrect_answers": ["17", "16", "28"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor plays officer Sadusky, the mason who happens to be serving as the chief police detective in the 2004 movie National Treasure?", "correct_answer": "Harvey Keitel", "incorrect_answers": ["Harrison Woods", "Christopher Plummer", "Sean Bean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the Great Lakes is situated entirely within the United States?", "correct_answer": "Lake Michigan", "incorrect_answers": ["Lake Erie", "Lake Huron", "Lake Superior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Christian Bale stars in the 2009 crime movie Public Enemies. What type of character does he play?", "correct_answer": "FBI agent", "incorrect_answers": ["Police officer", "Wealthy businessman", "Criminal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Magna Carta went into effect in 1215.  Who signed it?", "correct_answer": "nobody", "incorrect_answers": ["Eleanor of Aquitaine", "King John aka John Lackland", "King Richard the Lion Hearted"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Miracle, the U.S. team beat the second ranked team in the world. Which nation was this?", "correct_answer": "Czechoslovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Romania", "Russia", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the arm is bent in the elbow joint humans use the biceps branchii musle and the triceps is used when it is extended. What is the name of the muscle that abducts the arm in the shoulder?", "correct_answer": "Deltoid muscle", "incorrect_answers": ["Teres minor muscle", "Latissimus dorsi muscle", "Pectoralis major"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of the Republic of the Congo?", "correct_answer": "Brazzaville", "incorrect_answers": ["Lusaka", "Lima", "Libreville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fed up with your tattoo? There is a way to get rid of it. This is the most popular way of tattoo removal.", "correct_answer": "Laser treatment", "incorrect_answers": ["Dermabrasion", "Surgery", "Putting natural-colored ink over the tattoo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original reward  for killing the shark in the movie Jaws was 10,000 dollars.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1986, Sir Alex Ferguson became manager of this English Premier League soccer club, nicknamed The Red Devils.", "correct_answer": "Manchester United", "incorrect_answers": ["Chelsea", "Aston Villa", "Blackburn Rovers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following henchmen was the only one to appear in more than one James Bond movie?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Oddjob", "Pusssy Galore", "Goldfinger"]}]